enterprisenation.com 2012-06-15

# Privacy policy | Enterprise Nation, the small business community

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

We do not store credit card or any other financial information about our customers.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalise your experience

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * To improve our website

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * To improve customer service

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

  * To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Network Security

Enterprise Nation has put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information that is collected. Various security technologies have been implemented to ensure that external parties cannot access or modify Users’ personal information on Enterprise Nation. Specifically, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption is used on specific Web pages to safeguard online purchase transactions. SSL technology is the industry standard protocol for secure, Web-based communications.

### Financial Information

Customer payment information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) are all processed securely through the PayPal® (Website Payments Pro) service. Enterprise Nation does not store any Customer financial information on it’s own servers, OR in it’s own databases; regardless of whether you enter your financial information at Bitsy or directly through PayPal®. For more information about PayPal® and their privacy policies, please visit: ( www.paypal.com ).

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.enterprisenation.com

9 Town Walls

Shrewsbury, Shropshire SY1 1TW

United Kingdom

info@enterprisenation.com

01743 272555
